thinktarget.com 2006-06-15

# ThinkTarget

## Information Collection and Use

ThinkTarget.com has created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your personally identifiable information at the ThinkTarget.com's website. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our personal information collection and use practices and the choices that you can make concerning the use of your personal information. ThinkTarget.com sends all new members a welcome email message to verify and confirm their registration in our network. ThinkTarget.com  also uses emails to inform members of new membership benefits, features, subscriptions, contests, and to advise members of urgent problems on our website and to present special member-only opportunities to buy products and services that are appropriate to the interest of our members. ThinkTarget.com  stores its records in the United States of America but may perform some of its data processing outside of the United States of America. We will protect your information no matter where we process or store your data.

##  Links 

The ThinkTarget.com  website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. When leaving our website, be sure to read the privacy statements of each website that collects personally identifiable information. Our privacy statement applies solely to information collected on the ThinkTarget.com  website.

##  Security 

ThinkTarget.com  has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of members' information. We use industry standard procedures and processes to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as firewalls, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data.

Unfortunately, when you submit information about yourself to ThinkTarget.com  over the Internet the information may travel over many systems that are not under the control of ThinkTarget.com . To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate and typical physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

All employees, contractors and other companies engaged by ThinkTarget.com  for work that involves access to personal information are contractually required to keep the information confidential and not to use it in any way other than what is necessary to perform their work for ThinkTarget.com .

##  Unsolicited Email 

ThinkTarget.com  is committed to protecting the integrity of our web site. We encourage all members to promote ThinkTarget.com  with the highest standards of Internet etiquette and business ethics. ThinkTarget.com  strictly prohibits the sending of Unsolicited Email or electronic messages of any kind to unknown individuals or individuals that have not consented to receiving such information.

In addition, a member may not make any false or deceptive misrepresentations through Unsolicited Email or other advertising methods with respect to any and all compensation or products received from ThinkTarget.com or with respect to compensation or products that potential members are likely to receive.

##  Privacy for Children and Minors 

Protecting the privacy of children is important to ThinkTarget.com . For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from members known to be under 18, and no part of our website is designed to attract anyone under 18. It is important to remember that ThinkTarget.com  cannot always determine that a member is a child under the age of 18. Members under the age of 18 must have written parental consent to release their name, email address, or other personal information.

##  Cookies 

A cookie is information that a website transfers to your computer for record-keeping purposes. Cookies are typically used to save a user's password so that the user does not have to re-enter their password each time they visit the same website. In addition, cookies can make the Internet more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular website. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and most websites use them to provide useful features for their members. Most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can set your Internet browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a website if you do.

ThinkTarget.com  may use cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly and to deliver content specific to your interests and for statistical purposes. In the future, cookies may be used to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our website. Some of our advertisers or other partners may use cookies on our website, but we do not have access to or control over their cookies.

##  IP Address 

An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. All computer identification on the Internet is conducted with IP addresses, which allow computers and servers to recognize and communicate with each other. Your IP address does not contain your name but does provide additional demographic information.

ThinkTarget.com  will release IP addresses to advertisers or third parties. We use your IP address to help diagnose or detect problems with our server, for security reasons, to conduct system administration and site analysis, and to administer our website. Any demographic information collected from your IP address is added to you information and stored in our database for use by ThinkTarget.com  or third parties.

##  Cancel Your Membership 

If you cancel your membership, you are no longer eligible to receive your products and you will not receive free email offers or information about new promotions, contests or services. If you wish to cancel your membership, simply click on the membership link above.

##  Notification of Changes to the Privacy Policy 

The ThinkTarget.com  Privacy Policy may be updated to increase our members' privacy protection or to improve our information practices. If there are changes made in the future, the changes will not affect information already collected. Any changes to the ThinkTarget.com  Privacy Policy will be available on this page for members to review.

If you have any questions about the ThinkTarget.com  Privacy Policy, the information practices of this website, or you would like to view or change your personal information, send your request to:

ThinkTarget.com  
5444 Westhiemer Suite 1975  
Houston, TX 77056  
USA 

This ThinkTarget.com Privacy Policy is subject to change without notice. Please review this Privacy Policy on this website frequently to look for changes. Your continued membership will signify your unconditional acceptance to the modified terms.
